



Jihad Melhem

UI/UX Designer & Interior Designer

Personal Information

+961 70 599 077 jihad.melhem9@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Portfolio</u> Beirut, Lebanon As a professional with expertise in both UI/UX design and Interior design, I bring a unique set of skills to every project. I excel in creating user-centered interfaces that enhance the user experience and have a keen eye for detail. My deep understanding of spatial design enables me to conceptualize and execute both beautiful and functional interior spaces.

Education

Sep. 2016 - Oct. 2021

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Interior Design Arts, Science, & Technology University In Lebanon

Languages

Arabic: Native

English: Intermediate French: Intermediate

Softwares and Tools









Training & Certifications

UI/UX Design Bootcamp - SE Factory

Jul. 2024 - Sep. 2024

Completed an intensive UI/UX program covering the case study, principles of UI design, journey map, User low, competitor analysis, workshops, projects and the advanced level in figma, it's 6 weeks in addition to 2 weeks for the final project.

Projects

HoloFit App

Aug. 2024 - Sep. 2024

The app integrates with holographic projectors to deliver dynamic workout sessions, enabling users to enhance their fitness potential from the comfort of their homes.

Main Feature: HoloFit provides holographic projectors to create immersive, real-time 3D workout experiences. Users interact with lifelike 3D avatars and workout in various virtual environments, making fitness routines more engaging and enjoyable.

<u>PetCare</u> Jul. 2024 - Aug. 2024

The app offers integrated telehealth consultations, allowing pet owners to connect with veterinarians through video calls directly within the app

Main Feature: The app provides immediate access to professional advice, and treatment plans without the need for an in-person visit.

Work Experience

Sales Associate | Aishti | Home Collection

Nov. 2022 - Jul. 2024

- Met with customers to discuss design concepts, materials, and pricing options.
- Provided customers with product knowledge and answered questions regarding pricing, delivery details, or repair services.

Cashier | Gray Mackenzie

Feb. 2019 - Feb. 2022

- Handled cash, credit, or check transactions with customers.
- Scanned goods and collected payments.
- Ensured pricing was correct.
- Issued refunds, or changed tickets, and provided receipts.